Inventory to the Annelise Graebner Anderson Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office of Management and Budget, 1981-1983 (Box 28-139)
  - HUD 1984 Fall Director’s Review (Box-folder 43: 4-5)
  - SBA – 1984 Budget (Box-folder 43: 6)
  - Treasury (Box-folder 43: 7)
  - FCC (Box-folder 43: 8)
  - FEMA – 1984 Budget (Box-folder 43: 9)
  - GSA (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - Health Benefits (Box-folder 44: 2)
  - HUD (Box-folder 44: 3)
  - OPM – 1984 Budget (Box-folder 44: 4)
  - Clipping (Box-folder 44: 5)
  - A model of IRS direct revenue-related tax administration programs (Box-folder 44: 6)
  - Department of Defense – FY 1984 Fall Director’s Review (Box-folder 44: 7)
  - FHLBB FY 1984 Budget Hearing (Box-folder 44: 8)
  - Regulatory Reform (Box-folder 44: 9)
  - Spring Review Session (Box-folder 44: 10)
  - Budget accounting and structure issues (Box-folder 44: 11)
  - Senator Stevens’ Letter (Box-folder 44: 12)
  - Major Operating Costs of the Federal Government (Box-folder 44: 13)
  - Spring Review: Federal Credit (Box-folder 44: 14)
  - Spring Review: Minerals, etc. (Box-folder 44: 15)
  - Spring Review: Transportation (Box-folder 44: 16)
  - Spring Review (Box-folder 44: 17)
  - 1984 Budget (Box-folder 44: 18)
  - FY84 Budget Discretionary Freeze Book (Box-folder 45: 1)
  - FY84 Budget Preliminary Budget Resolution 302 (a) analysis book (Box-folder 45: 2)
  - Tax Proposals – February 13, 1981 (Box-folder 45: 3)
  - DC ’84 Budget (Box-folder 45: 4)
  - Budget Planning (Box-folder 45: 5-9)
  - 84 Budget: agency specific (Box-folder 46: 1)
  - Side-By-Side – Arranged by Senate Committee followed by Block Grants (Box-folder 46: 2-5)
  - Budget Working Group Meeting – February 7, 1981 (Box-folder 46: 6-7)
  - Economic Program Working Group – February 12, 1981 (Box-folder 46: 8)
  - Budget Working Group Notes – January 29, 1981 (Box-folder 46: 9)
  - Economic Program Working Group – February 13, 1981 (Box-folder 46: 10-11)
  - OEOB (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - Director’s Briefing Book Vol. I (Box-folder 47: 2)
  - Director’s Review FY 82 Information Collection Budget (Box-folder 47: 3)
  - 1983 Spring Planning Review (Box-folder 47: 4)
  - JTGMD Division Director’s Review FY 1983 Budget (Box-folder 47: 5)
  - DOJ Director’s Appeals Materials (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - Backup material for the program proposals in the president’s budget reform plan (Box-folder 48: 2)
  - 1981 JGMB Discussion Papers (Box-folder 48: 3)
  - 1981 Spring Planning Review Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box-folder 48: 4)
  - DOC/SBA 1983 Director’s Appeals Materials (Box-folder 48: 5)
  - Draft HUD issues and PAD issues for 83 (Box-folder 48: 6)
  - Budget Review Sessions Material – November 9, 1982 (Box-folder 48: 7-8)
  - Fall Step-Down Process/Economic assumptions/OMB central budget management system (Box-folder 49: 1-2)
  - Notes (Box-folder 49: 3)
  - Senate Committee on Commerce Science and Transportation (Box-folder 49: 4)
  - Problem Bills (Box-folder 49: 5)
  - 1982 Reagan Budget Department of Commerce and SBA – back up materials (Box-folder 49: 6)
  - Senate Appropriations Committee GOP Members, Mtg. #10 – February 3, 1981 (Box-folder 49: 7)
  - Department of Commerce (Box-folder 49: 8)
  - Senate Budget Committee’s markup (Box-folder 49: 9)
  - Budget – National Defense (Box-folder 49: 10)
  - Budget Authority by Function and Program (Box-folder 49: 11)
  - 1981 Change Bill (Box-folder 50: 1)
  - Outlays by function and program (Box-folder 50: 2)
  - Budget Notes (Box-folder 50: 3)
  - Budget Amendments (Box-folder 50: 4)
  - Notes (Box-folder 50: 5)
  - Thrift Bailouts Briefing Book (Box-folder 50: 6-7)
  - Transportation (Box-folder 50: 8)
  - Transportation (Box-folder 51: 1-2)
  - First Budget Resolution for Fiscal Year 1982 (Box-folder 51: 3)
  - 84 Budget – FOK 10/14/82 mtg. to establish tentative ceilings (Box-folder 51: 4)
  - CBMS runs (Box-folder 51: 5)
  - Major Themes (Box-folder 51: 6)
  - 84 Budget/Revenues (Box-folder 51: 7)
  - OMB 1984 Ceilings (Box-folder 51: 8)
  - Budget Briefings (Box-folder 51: 9)
  - The President’s FY 1984 Budget Freeze and Reform Plan (Box-folder 51: 10)
  - Testimony of the Honorable David Stockman (Box-folder 51: 11)
  - Budget Notes (Box-folder 51: 12)
  - Summary of the Reconciliation Conference (Box-folder 52: 1)
  - 84 Budget – FOK 10/14/82 mtg. to establish tentative ceilings (Box-folder 52: 2)
  - Fiscal Year 1982 revised second budget resolution recommendations (Box-folder 52: 3)
  - Comprehensive Budget Freeze and Economic Recovery Plan (Box-folder 52: 4)
  - Budget Notes (Box-folder 52: 5)
  - Thrifts-CCEA Papers (Box-folder 52: 6)
  - Deposit Interest Rate Ceilings and Housing Credit (Box-folder 52: 7)
  - Financial Institution Reform: Past actions proposed reforms (Box-folder 52: 8)
  - Thrifts – General/Misc. (Box-folder 52: 9)
  - Thrifts ICC’s (Box-folder 52: 10)
  - The Report of the Interagency Task Force on Thrift Institutions (Box-folder 52: 11)
  - Thrift Stimulus Briefing Book (Box-folder 52: 12)
  - Current Industry Status (Box-folder 53: 1)
  - Gramm-Latta II (Box-folder 53: 2)
  - Broyhill Energy + Commerce minority reconciliation package (Box-folder 53: 3)
  - Economic Recovery Tax Act of 1981 (Box-folder 53: 4)
  - Budget Authority and Outlays Authorization (Box-folder 53: 5)
  - Administration Substitute Table (Box-folder 53: 6)
  - Legislative Affairs Meeting – June 16, 1981 (Box-folder 53: 7)
  - Domenici Press Conference (Box-folder 53: 8)
  - FSLIC Apportionments (Box-folder 53: 9)
  - Adjustable Rate Mortgages (Box-folder 53: 10)
  - Thrifts – Mark-to-Market (Box-folder 53: 11)
  - Financial Deregulation TF (Box-folder 53: 12)
  - GNMA and FHA/PMI Discussion at CCEA (Box-folder 53: 13)
  - FHLMC (Box-folder 53: 14-15)
  - FNMA (Box-folder 53: 16)
  - GNMA (Box-folder 53: 17)
  - Notes on Budget (Box-folder 54: 1-3)
  - Committee on Energy and Commerce (Box-folder 54: 4)
  - Gramm-Latta (Box-folder 54: 5)
  - 1984 HUD Budget PAD Issues Index (Box-folder 54: 6)
  - Summary of Fiscal Year 1983 Spending Recommendations by Function (Box-folder 54: 7)
  - Senate Staff Analysis of Reconciliation Bills (Box-folder 54: 8)
  - Gramm-Latta II (Box-folder 54: 9)
  - “Trouble Spots” in Reconciliation Bills (Box-folder 54: 10)
  - Complete Rewrite of Minority Side-By-Side (Box-folder 54: 11)
  - Conrail (Box-folder 54: 12)
  - Budget Status 83 (Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Reagan’s initiatives to reduce regulatory burdens/Program for Economic Recovery (Box-folder 55: 2)
  - COLA Policy for the 1984 Budget (Box-folder 55: 3)
  - Wrapping Up Entitlements (Box-folder 55: 4)
  - Scorekeeping Report (4) – Dec. 21 (Box-folder 55: 5)
  - A Program for Economic Recovery (Box-folder 55: 6)
  - Revised March 10 Budget Revision Document (Box-folder 55: 7)
  - Fact Sheets Fairness Book Papers (Box-folder 55: 8)
  - Misc. budget notes (Box-folder 55: 9)
  - Remaining Reagan Budget Issues – February 1981 (Box-folder 55: 10-12)
  - Remaining Reagan Budget Issues (Box-folder 56: 1-2)
  - Administratively Confidential (Box-folder 56: 3)
  - March 15 Reports (Box-folder 56: 4)
  - Summaries of outstanding issues – February 23, 1981 (Box-folder 56: 5)
  - OUT (Box-folder 56: 6)
  - FY 1982 Budget Further Reductions – February 2, 1981 (Box-folder 56: 7)
  - Reagan Budget Reductions “C” List (Box-folder 56: 8-10)
  - Director’s Briefing Book Volume IV (Box-folder 57: 1-2)
  - HUD issues (Box-folder 57: 3-5)
  - Subsidized Housing (Box-folder 57: 6)
  - Housing Flap (Box-folder 57: 7)
  - Lugar Bill (Box-folder 57: 8)
  - Journal Articles – 1982 (Box-folder 57: 9)
  - TIM Proposal (Box-folder 57: 10)
  - Housing Deregulation (Box-folder 57: 11)
  - Lugar Bill Veto (Box-folder 57: 12)
  - PAD Briefing SBA/DOC 1982 Budget Revisions (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - Housing Stimulus (Box-folder 58: 2)
  - Housing Affordability in an Inflationary Environment (Box-folder 58: 3)
  - DAS Talking Points (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - Corcoran mtg. with Pres (Box-folder 58: 5)
  - Analysis of Homebuilder Estimates (Box-folder 58: 6)
  - Costs of the Lugar Proposal (Box-folder 58: 7)
  - Notes on Lugar (Box-folder 58: 8)
  - Critique of the Lugar Bill (Box-folder 58: 9)
  - FAF Talking Points (Box-folder 58: 10)
  - Notes on Housing (Box-folder 58: 11-12)
  - LANDSAT (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Civil Defense (Box-folder 59: 2)
  - Federalism – 1984 (Box-folder 59: 3)
  - Federal Property (Box-folder 59: 4)
  - FTC (Box-folder 59: 5)
  - Historical/Timing (Box-folder 59: 6)
  - HUD Authorization/FY 83 (Box-folder 59: 7)
  - The Left (Box-folder 59: 8)
  - Olympics (Box-folder 59: 9)
  - Pres. Statements and Drafts (Box-folder 59: 10)
  - Director’s Pronouncements (Box-folder 59: 11)
  - State of the Union 83 (Box-folder 59: 12)
  - Republican Housing Proposals (Box-folder 59: 13)
  - Housing Bailout (Box-folder 59: 14-15)
  - Conference (Box-folder 59: 16)
  - Conference (Box-folder 60: 1-3)
  - Unemployment (Box-folder 60: 4)
  - Social Security (Box-folder 60: 5)
  - OMB as agency (Box-folder 60: 6)
  - Minority Business (Box-folder 60: 7)
  - Apportionments (Box-folder 60: 8-9)
  - Deferral of Budget Authority (Box-folder 61: 1)
  - Justification of Estimates for the 1983 Appropriations Request (Box-folder 61: 2)
  - Status Report on Subconferences and Calendar of Upcoming Meetings on the Omnibus Reconciliation Act of 1981 (Box-folder 61: 3-4)
  - Conference – SBA (Box-folder 61: 5)
  - Conference – commerce, sci., transp. (Box-folder 61: 6)
  - Conference/Transportation (Box-folder 61: 7)
  - Conference/Banking (Box-folder 61: 8)
  - CDBG and UDAG (Box-folder 61: 9)
  - Subsidized Housing Alternatives (Box-folder 61: 10)
  - 1983 ceiling and planning documents (Box-folder 61: 11)
  - Notes on HUD (Box-folder 61: 12)
  - Notes on HUD/Outlays (Box-folder 61: 13)
  - Changes to Appropriations Requests (Box-folder 61: 14)
  - 1983 Budget (Box-folder 61: 15)
  - Senate Continuing Resolution (Box-folder 62: 1-3)
  - Senate Amendments (Box-folder 62: 4)
  - Deficiency Apportionments (Box-folder 62: 5)
  - Appropriations (Box-folder 62: 6-7)
  - Appropriations – Treas/Postal (Box-folder 62: 8)
  - Appropriations – Transportation (Box-folder 63: 1)
  - Appropriations – General (Box-folder 63: 2)
  - Appropriations – D.C. (Box-folder 63: 3)
  - Appropriations – State, DOJ, DOC. (Box-folder 63: 4)
  - Appropriations – Other (Box-folder 63: 5)
  - 1983 Cuts (Box-folder 63: 6)
  - Federalism (Box-folder 63: 7)
  - CAB (Box-folder 63: 8)
  - Entitlements and Budget (Box-folder 63: 9)
  - Small Agencies (Box-folder 63: 10)
  - Deferral Problem (Box-folder 63: 11)
  - Transportation/Existing or Agency-Sponsored User Fee Proposals (Box-folder 63: 12)
  - S533 (Box-folder 63: 13)
  - South Florida Task Force (Box-folder 63: 14)
  - SILVER (Box-folder 63: 15)
  - Regulatory Overview (Box-folder 63: 16)
  - House/Senate Committees (Box-folder 63: 17)
  - Misc. notes/memorandums (Box-folder 64: 1-2)
  - Cabinet Council Economic Affairs Working Group on Credit Policy (Box-folder 64: 3)
  - Justice, Treasury, General Management (Box-folder 64: 4)
  - Proposed Changes in the Congressional Budget Process (Box-folder 64: 5)
  - Reaganomics and the President’s Men (Box-folder 64: 6)
  - The Fairness Issue and the Administration’s Fortunes (Box-folder 64: 7)
  - Immigration/Refugee (Box-folder 64: 8)
  - Draft of Budget Act Reform Testimony (Box-folder 64: 9)
  - Tracking Log as of October 7, 1982 (Box-folder 64: 10)
  - Talking Points on Housing (Box-folder 64: 11)
  - Urgent Supplements (Box-folder 64: 12)
  - Urgent Supplements (Box-folder 65: 1)
  - Ninety-Seventh Congress of the United States of America (Box-folder 65: 2)
  - Housing Bill (Box-folder 65: 3)
  - Lugar Compromise (Box-folder 65: 4)
  - Senate Floor Action (Box-folder 65: 5)
  - Bureau of Government Financial Operations (BGFO) (Box-folder 65: 6)
  - Amendment (Box-folder 65: 7)
  - BATF/South Florida Task Activities (Box-folder 65: 8)
  - The Case Against Bailouts (Box-folder 65: 9)
  - Misc. Notes (Box-folder 65: 10)
  - Petition of Continental Air Lines, Inc. for Rulemaking (Box-folder 65: 11)
  - Pending Enrolled Bills (Box-folder 65: 12)
  - Tracking Log – December 10, 1982 (Box-folder 65: 13)
  - FFB (Box-folder 65: 14)
  - Consolidated Federal Primary Inspection (Box-folder 65: 15)
  - HUD/GNMA Tandem 1983 Appropriation (Box-folder 65: 16)
  - Economic Mobility Commission (Box-folder 65: 17)
  - Status Report on Open Budget Items (Box-folder 65: 18)
  - Apportionment Under The Further Continuing Appropriations for 1983 (Box-folder 65: 19)
  - Special Studies (Box-folder 65: 20)
  - 1983 Re-estimates (Box-folder 65: 21)
  - 1982/1983 Outlays (Box-folder 65: 22)
  - Budget Defense (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - User Fees – Combined Effort (Box-folder 66: 2-3)
  - Transp., Commerce, Housing (Box-folder 66: 4)
  - February 25, 1982 Hearing Senate Governmental Affairs (Box-folder 66: 5-7)
  - 1981/1982 Poverty – def. (Box-folder 67: 1)
  - Memorandum to Michael J. Horowitz (Box-folder 67: 2)
  - Interstate Resurfacing, Restoration and Rehabilitation Study/Notes (Box-folder 67: 3)
  - Third Credit Book for the Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs Credit Policy Working Group (Box-folder 67: 4)
  - Briefing Book for 3/16/81 Hearing on FTC, CPSC, and IRS (Box-folder 67: 5)
  - Coast Guard Roles and Missions (Box-folder 67: 6)
  - Small Business Administration 1982 Briefing Material (Box-folder 67: 7-8)
  - Summary of DOE Budget Appeal/BWG Issue Papers (Box-folder 67: 9)
  - Summary of DOE Budget Appeal/BWG Issue Papers (Box-folder 68: 1)
  - Coast Guard Budget (Box-folder 68: 2)
  - Briefing for Deputy Director March 1982 (Box-folder 68: 3)
  - FY 1982 Information Collection Budget (ICB) (Box-folder 68: 4)
  - Monetary Trends/Economic Report (Box-folder 68: 5)
  - Budget Appeal (Box-folder 68: 6)
  - IRS (Box-folder 68: 7)
  - Background (Box-folder 68: 8)
  - Department of Treasury Planned Fees and Reimbursement/Staff Recommendations (Box-folder 68: 9)
  - Treasury Revenue Projections (Box-folder 68: 10)
  - Treasury Revenue Enhancement Initiatives (Box-folder 68: 11)
  - IRS’s Proposal for Direct Deposit of Estimated Tax Payments (Box-folder 69: 1)
  - IRS Staff Data/Treasury Package/Letter from Egger and McNamar (Box-folder 69: 2)
  - Revenue Requests (Box-folder 69: 3)
  - December 7, 8, or 9 1981 on FY 83 Budget (Box-folder 69: 4)
  - Department of the Treasury Appeal Notes (Box-folder 69: 5)
  - Treasury Views Concerning the OMB Allowance for FY 1983 Budget (Box-folder 69: 6)
  - Summary of Funding and Planning Levels (Box-folder 69: 7)
  - Agenda – January 27, 1983 (Box-folder 69: 8)
  - Meeting with State Legislators (Box-folder 69: 9)
  - Cabinet Council on Legal Policy – February 10, 1983 (Box-folder 69: 10)
  - Possible Bipartisan Compromise on Jobs and Humanitarian Aid (Box-folder 69: 11)
  - External Debt Problems of Developing Countries (Box-folder 69: 12)
  - Weekly Activities Report – TCH Division – Week Ending February 10, 1983 (Box-folder 69: 13)
  - Trade Organization Study (Box-folder 69: 14)
  - Memorandums (Box-folder 69: 15)
  - HUD Book (Box-folder 69: 16)
  - Official Definition of Poverty (Box-folder 69: 17)
  - Stats on the Exposure of U.S. Banks in Foreign Countries (Box-folder 69: 18)
  - Articles (Box-folder 69: 19)
  - Suggestions for Increasing Efficiency, Fairness and Economy in the U.S. Patent Office (Box-folder 69: 20)
  - Infrastructure/Public Works (Box-folder 69: 21)
  - Federal Retirement (Box-folder 69: 22)
  - Address by David A. Stockman – February 10, 1983 (Box-folder 69: 23)
  - Civil Service Retirement (Box-folder 69: 24)
  - CCNRE (Box-folder 69: 25)
  - Fact Sheet on FY 1983 Urgent Supplement (Box-folder 70: 1)
  - Budget Supplementals Report (Box-folder 70: 2)
  - U.S. Financial Data/Personnel (Box-folder 70: 3)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box-folder 70: 4)
  - Daily Legislative Highlights Report (Box-folder 70: 5)
  - Federal Credit/Federal Financing Bank (Box-folder 70: 6)
  - Federal Maritime Commission (FMC) (Box-folder 70: 7)
  - Federal Personnel Pay (Box-folder 70: 8)
  - Update on Mutual Savings Bank Mergers in New York City (Box-folder 70: 9)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) (Box-folder 70: 10)
  - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) (Box-folder 70: 11)
  - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) (Box-folder 70: 12)
  - Performance Based Incentive System (PBIS) (Box-folder 70: 13)
  - FEHB (Box-folder 70: 14)
  - Freddie Mac (Box-folder 70: 15)
  - 1984 Budget Planning Exercise (Box-folder 70: 16-17)
  - Department of the Treasury – November 27, 1981 (Box-folder 71: 1)
  - Department of Transportation Issue Paper – Highway Taxes (Box-folder 71: 2)
  - Highways (Box-folder 71: 3)
  - Transportation Notes (Box-folder 71: 4)
  - “Balance of Budget Authority” and “Object Class Analysis” reports (Box-folder 71: 5)
  - Increased Paycosts for Fiscal Year 1982 (Box-folder 71: 6)
  - Outlay Effects of Revised Economic Assumptions: March 1981 vs January 1982 (Box-folder 71: 7)
  - Statement By Secretary of the Treasury Donald T. Regan at a Press Briefing on the Budget – February 6, 1982 (Box-folder 71: 8)
  - 1983 Budget Charts (Box-folder 71: 9)
  - Testimony of the Honorable David A. Stockman Before the Task Force on Entitlements of the House committee on the Budget (Box-folder 71: 10)
  - Budget – Tables (Box-folder 71: 11)
  - The President’s FY ’83 Budget and Fiscal Program (Box-folder 71: 12)
  - Part 5 (Box-folder 71: 13)
  - Memorandums (Box-folder 71: 14)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) (Box-folder 71: 15)
  - FY 1983 Historical Tables (Box-folder 71: 16)
  - Department of Transportation (Box-folder 71: 17)
  - Columbia River System (Box-folder 71: 18)
  - Federal Law Enforcement (Box-folder 71: 19)
  - Department Summary of Major Accomplishments – April 1981 (Box-folder 71: 20)
  - FY 1983 Spring Planning Review (Box-folder 71: 21)
  - Export Financing (Box-folder 71: 22)
  - Financial Adjustment Factor (FAF) (Box-folder 71: 23)
  - FAA (Box-folder 72: 1)
  - DAS Notes (Box-folder 72: 2)
  - Postal Service Monopoly (Box-folder 72: 3)
  - Tracking Log – October 8, 1982 (Box-folder 72: 4)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box-folder 72: 5)
  - CCMA (Box-folder 72: 6)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board (FHLBB) (Box-folder 72: 7)
  - Fact Sheets on State of the Union Address (Box-folder 72: 8)
  - The President’s FY 1984 Budget Freeze and Reform Plan (Box-folder 72: 9)
  - Highway/Mass Transit Legislation (Box-folder 72: 10)
  - Highway User Fees (Box-folder 72: 11)
  - Department of Transportation Issues (Box-folder 72: 12-14)
  - Tax Policy (Box-folder 72: 15)
  - Cabinet Issues (Box-folder 72: 16)
  - 1983 Appropriations (Box-folder 73: 1)
  - Appropriations (Box-folder 73: 2-3)
  - First Option for Reducing Size of FY 1983 Budget Amendment (Box-folder 73: 4)
  - Senate Appropriation Committee Table (Box-folder 73: 5)
  - Trade Policy (Box-folder 73: 6)
  - Cabinet Council on Commerce and Trade (Box-folder 73: 7)
  - 1983 FSLIC Reapportionment (Box-folder 73: 8)
  - Retail Sales for December (Box-folder 73: 9)
  - Cabinet Council on Management and Administration Minutes (Box-folder 73: 10)
  - Narcotics Trafficking (Box-folder 73: 11-12)
  - Criminal Justice Assistance Legislation (Box-folder 73: 13)
  - Real Growth in U.S. Defense Budget/Non-Defense Budget Growth Reductions (Box-folder 73: 14)
  - The Balanced Monetary Policy and Price Stability Act (Box-folder 73: 15)
  - Tracking Log – October 29, 1982 (Box-folder 73: 16)
  - Capital Formation (Box-folder 73: 17)
  - Briefing Papers for CCCT Information (Box-folder 73: 18)
  - Enrolled Bill H.R. 6211 (Box-folder 73: 19)
  - Letter from Domenici to Lugar Regarding Transit Funding (Box-folder 73: 20)
  - U.S. Export Controls: Issues for High Technology Industries (Box-folder 73: 21)
  - District of Columbia 1982 Annual Financial Report Highlights (Box-folder 73: 22)
  - Failure of the House to Pass Appropriations Bills (Box-folder 74: 1)
  - Close Hold – Document Book (Box-folder 74: 2)
  - Detailed Chapter 2 Outline (Box-folder 74: 3)
  - Patent User Fees (Box-folder 74: 4)
  - Revised Enrolled Bill Listing (Box-folder 74: 5)
  - Cabinet Council on Legal Policy – January 26, 1983 (Box-folder 74: 6)
  - Background for DAS on National Holidays (Box-folder 74: 7)
  - Automation of Public Debt Accounts by the Federal Reserve (Box-folder 74: 8)
  - Farm Program Outlays (Box-folder 74: 9)
  - Memorandums/Notes (Box-folder 74: 10)
  - Articles (Box-folder 74: 11)
  - FTC Appeals (Box-folder 74: 12)
  - Justice Appeal (Box-folder 74: 13)
  - Schedules (Box-folder 74: 14)
  - HUD Testimony (Box-folder 74: 15-16)
  - Transportation Appeal (Box-folder 74: 17)
  - Treasury Appeal (Box-folder 74: 18)
  - MARAD (Box-folder 74: 19)
  - Commerce Appeal (Box-folder 75: 1)
  - A List Originals (Box-folder 75: 2)
  - HUD (Box-folder 75: 3)
  - Commerce (Box-folder 75: 4)
  - Department of Transportation Budget Working Group Decisions (Box-folder 75: 5)
  - Highway Trust Funds (Box-folder 75: 6)
  - Motor Fuels Tax Options (Box-folder 75: 7)
  - EDA and OPTI Recruits (Box-folder 75: 8)
  - Federal Subsidies – Conrail (Box-folder 75: 9)
  - Rail Fixed Guideway Budget (Box-folder 75: 10)
  - Mass Transport – Energy (Box-folder 75: 11)
  - SBA (Box-folder 75: 12)
  - Background Material for Testimony before the Subcommittee on Economic Development of the House Committee on Public Works (Box-folder 75: 13)
  - Supporting Justification Materials (Box-folder 75: 14)
  - HUD Budget Items (Box-folder 75: 15)
  - Status Report on Decisions – Energy and Science Division/Justice and General Management Branch (Box-folder 75: 16)
  - Summary Fact Sheet – A Program for Economic Recovery (Box-folder 75: 17)
  - Implementing Proposals (Box-folder 75: 18)
  - Budget Appeals (Box-folder 75: 19)
  - Status of Executive Office Budget Revisions (Box-folder 75: 20)
  - Outlays – Cuts/Carter Budget/Rescission Proposals in the President’s February 18 Message (Box-folder 75: 21)
  - Issues to be Resolved by Feb 26th for Revised 1982 Budget (Box-folder 75: 22)
  - Requirements for the March 10 Budget (Box-folder 75: 23)
  - DOT (Box-folder 75: 24)
  - UMTA (Box-folder 75: 25)
  - Cooperative Automative Research Program (CARP) (Box-folder 75: 26)
  - Airline Subsidies (Box-folder 75: 27)
  - Federal Subsidies – Conrail (Box-folder 75: 28)
  - Federal Highway Administration (Box-folder 75: 29)
  - Conrail (Box-folder 75: 30)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission (ARC)/Presidential Appeals (Box-folder 75: 31)
  - Agency Appeals (Box-folder 76: 1)
  - HUD Appeal (Box-folder 76: 2-3)
  - Questions and Answers for Democrats and the President’s Interview (Box-folder 76: 4)
  - Salomon Brothers – Comments on Credit (Box-folder 76: 5)
  - Lists of Previously – Rejected Reductions (Box-folder 76: 6)
  - Programs for Termination (Box-folder 76: 7)
  - Revisions to the 1982 Budget (Box-folder 76: 8)
  - 11/4 82 Data Base Policy Levels (Box-folder 76: 9)
  - Budget Review Session – November 3, 1982 (Box-folder 76: 10)
  - Budget Review Session – November 2, 1982 (Box-folder 76: 11)
  - Retail Sales in September (Box-folder 76: 12)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs (CCEA) – Financial Markets Update (Box-folder 76: 13)
  - Econ Assumptions (Box-folder 76: 14)
  - National Defense and International (Box-folder 76: 15)
  - Budget Review Session – November 8, 1982 (Box-folder 76: 16)
  - Washington Post and copies of discretionary funding memos –September 30, 1982 (Box-folder 76: 17)
  - Minutes of CCEA Meeting (11/2) (Box-folder 76: 18)
  - Budget Outlook and Options (Box-folder 76: 19)
  - Retail Sales in October (Box-folder 76: 20)
  - Summary of Reductions in U.S. Domestic Spending (Box-folder 76: 21)
  - Budget Outlook Drafts (Box-folder 76: 22)
  - Defense Presentation (Box-folder 76: 23)
  - Monetary Perspectives (Box-folder 76: 24)